<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Asim Jofa</string>

    <string name="title_home">PRODUCTS</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">PROFILE</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">STORES</string>
    <string name="title_cart"></string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="activity_title_cart">Cart</string>
    <string name="title_info">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="title_about">about</string>
    <string name="profile_toolbar_title">Asim Jofa</string>

    <string name="terms">terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="agree">privacy policy</string>

    <string name="access_code">Access Code</string>
    <string name="pay_button">Pay</string>
    <string name="merchant_id">Merchant Id</string>
    <string name="currency">Currency</string>
    <string name="amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="redirect_url">Redirect Url</string>
    <string name="cancel_url">Cancel Url</string>
    <string name="rsa_url">RSA Key Url</string>

    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">LOVE MUSIC</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">This season top 20 albums</string>
    <string name="No_network_connection">No network connection</string>
    <string name="Internal_error">Internal error, please try it later</string>
    <string name="Filter_unavailable">Filter is unavailable</string>
    <string name="Product">Product</string>
    <string name="Your_cart_is_empty">Your cart is Empty</string>
    <string name="prouct_not_found">Related product not found</string>

    <string name="shipping_charger">FREE Shipping within Pakistan</string>
    <string name="payment_name">Select Payment Method</string>

    <string name="spinner_prompt_name">Select Size</string>
    <string name="google_api_keyy">AIzaSyAerYTzd3jWccNT3nDhxPXC3XDBSREpSlM</string>

    <string name="currency_change">Currency Change</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="infoText"><br/> + <font color="blue"> Info </font></string>

    //contact screen text
    <string name="monday_timing">Monday To Saturday from 9:00 Am to 9:00 Pm PST</string>
    <string name="sunday_timing">Sunday from 11:00 Am to 6:00Pm</string>
    <string name="select_country">Select Country</string>
    
    //privacy policy content
    <string name="accuracy_text">&#160;We have taken every care in the preparation of the content of this website, in particular to ensure that prices quoted
        are correct at time of publishing and all products have been fairly described. However, orders will only be accepted
        if there are no material errors in the description of the goods or their prices as advertised on this website. Packaging may vary
        from that shown. The weights, dimensions and capacities given are approximate only. We have made every effort to display as accurately
        as possible the colors of our products that appear on the website. However, as the actual colors you see will depend on your monitor,
        we cannot guarantee that your monitors display of any color will accurately reflect the color of the product on delivery.</string>
    <string name="shipping_text">Our shipping timing for orders DELIVERY within PAKISTAN will be 2 weeks or it will be informed on order
        confirmation, any delays will be informed accordingly, or if not informed it may be because of no communication (Email / Phone) working
        or defined and for INTERNATIONAL Customers’ delivery time will be 14-20 working days after the payment confirmation (Bank Transfer).
        There can be unexpected delivery delays due to custom clearance or may be any undefined reason. The delay can further go up to 5-6 working days or more. We are not
        responsible for any kind of delays nor if that delay is not informed to customer for Domestic or International customers who gave order using
        any kind of payment method.</string>
    <string name="delivery_txt">Delivery charges may vary depending on the type of products ordered and the location you select and cannot be refunded. We take no responsibility it
        there are any additional charges in terms of custom or duties charged by local authorities / Governments (Out of Pakistan). The custom charges have to be borne by the customer.</string>

    <string name="order_text">We shall try our level best to make deliveries in the most reasonable time possible. But order deliveries may
        be delayed in case of certain unexpected situations; we do not assume
        any responsibility of delayed deliveries, though it does everything in its power to avoid them.</string>

    <string name="text_order_place">1.&#160;International customers can make payment through bank transfer. The order that you place is kept on hold for 36 hours
        after you receive a confirmation email / call from us about the order and payment details. If you plan to make payment after 36 hours of receiving
        the confirmation, please confirm it with us if the products that you have ordered are still in stock.\n
        2.&#160;The Asim Jofa Store(s) takes no guarantee of the products availability that you had ordered, if you are making the payment after the given timeframe. Though our
        efforts will be to process your initial order, but if any of the ordered products is out of stock you will be offered to choose any other product/design/color
        (within the same price range). We will not be held responsible if there are delays in delivery due to out of stock products.
        (within the same price range). We will not be held responsible if there are delays in delivery due to out of stock products.\n
        3.&#160;If we get no confirmation from the customer, the order might be cancelled without any notification.\n
        4.&#160;The International order is processed only after the international customer makes the payment.\n
        5.&#160;The customers within Pakistan can place the order online with confirmation for payment upon delivery.</string>
    //tab text
    <string name="exchange_policy">An exchange will only occur in the unlikely situation that we have sent you a defective or incorrect item, and only in the even
        the purchased goods is unused and undamaged by the customer. All lawn sales, and custom orders are non-exchangeable.</string>
    <string name="return_policy">All orders are final, and non refundable, but you can exchange in an event where an incorrect item has been mailed to you.
        We can only exchange the purchased items subject to product and size availability. 
        Any exchange/returns should be brought to our notice with one-week of the receipt. Any claims made afterwards would not be honored.</string>
    <string name="refund_policy">All sales are considered final. There are no monetary returns, but can be exchanged for products of equal or higher value.</string>

    <string name="forget_text">If you have forgotten your password, enter your email address and we will send you instructions to retrieve it. </string>
    <string name="copy_code">When you get code successfully copy that code and paste(within 2-3 min) in to your login account and then update your password with the same code</string>
    <string name="change_password_text">If you want to change your password, enter password and new password. </string>
    <string name="tab_online">OLINE</string>
    <string name="tab_store">STORE</string>
    <string name="com_care_string">Pure chiffon thread  (depend on parent category)\n
        Care:\n
        Hand washes recommended. \n
        Do not bleach.\n
        Iron with care.\n
        Do not Tumble dry.\n
    </string>

</resources>
